schoolsnet.com 2017-09-06

# Schoolsnet is the No1 schools guide for parents, by parents

## 1 Introduction

1.1 At Schoolsnet, we understand the importance of keeping your personal information private. We set out our privacy practices and policies in this privacy policy. Please read it in conjunction with our terms of use as the terms incorporate this policy.

1.2 You do not need to give us any information to browse our website, but when you fill in the registration form, we do ask you for information about yourself.

1.3 On registration, you will be asked to 'opt in' to our privacy policy, ie to confirm that you agree to our use of any personally-identifiable information that we may collect from you in connection with your use of our website. By 'opting-in' you agree to our use of your information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.

1.4 If you have any queries about this privacy policy please email [contact@schoolsnet.com](mailto:contact@schoolsnet.com).

## 2 Personal Information we collect about you

2.1 As a visitor, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

2.2 When you register, we may collect some or all of the following information about you:

  * your name;
  * username;
  * email address;
  * password;
  * your postcode;
  * and other information necessary to complete your registration.

2.3 In this privacy policy, we refer to the information above and any other personally identifiable information that we may request from you and that you may provide to us as "personal information".

## 3 Our use of your personal information

3.1 We use personal information in the following ways:

  * to enable you to use any services that we may from time to time provide through our website;
  * to enable you to participate in competitions and offers for certain products and services which may be of interest to you, unless you inform us otherwise;
  * to enable you to receive newsletters from us;
  * to conduct market research surveys;
  * to send you updates about our website;
  * to provide you with information about products and services we offer;
  * for general research purposes, to allow us to develop the products and services we can offer to you; and
  * for website administration (including enabling us to respond to any comments on our website or feedback you may give us).

3.2 By agreeing to our privacy policy, you indicate your consent for us to use your personal information in the ways set out above. If, however, you do not wish to receive certain newsletters and other mailings from us relating to our own products and services and those of organisations with whom we have a strategic relationship, please email us at [contact@schoolsnet.com](mailto:contact@schoolsnet.com).

## 4 Disclosures

4.1 Your personal information may be passed to and used by our group companies in connection with providing services to you over our website and delivering or making our services available to you. Please note that some of our group companies may be located overseas in countries which do not have as extensive data protection laws as in the United Kingdom. For example, our software developers require certain test data (which may consist of personal information) and they are based in India.

4.2 We may also disclose your personal information in the following instances: (i) if we are required to do so by applicable law or under a court or similar order; (ii) as deemed necessary, in our discretion, to protect our legal rights or property or the legal rights or property of a Member or third party, or to prevent personal injury; and/or (iii) in connection with a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of our assets or stock or our affiliated entities (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

## 5 Hyperlinks to other web sites

5.1 This website contains hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties which are beyond our control. These other sites have their own privacy policies and we urge you to review them, because this privacy policy will not apply. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third-party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk.

5.2 We generally do not object to you linking directly to the homepage of our website, although we reserve the right to refuse our authorisation to such linking at our sole discretion. We do not permit our pages to be loaded into frames on your website; our web pages must load into the user's entire window.

5.3 We reserve the right to move or change our website URL at any time in order to meet changing business needs and to continually improve our online service. External websites link to our website at their own risk.

## 6 Cookies

6.1 When you view or use our website we may store information on the hard drive of your computer in the form of a "cookie" (essentially a small text file). Cookies allow us to tailor our website to your interests and preferences. For example, a cookie might contain information about the web pages you have visited on our website, which could allow us to customise your next visit to our website. Cookies, however, do not allow us access to the rest of your computer and we do not use them to collect personally identifiable information about you.

6.2 Most internet browsers enable you to delete cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored on your hard drive. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about how to do this. However, should you decide to disable any cookies we place on your computer you may not be able to use certain services or facilities on our website.

6.3 You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on our website. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the internet industry.

## 7 Search Engine

When you use our search engine, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies and other tracking technologies described above. For example, when you use our search engine, we may keep track of which search terms are popular. If we display advertising to you on our website (including the search results pages displayed after any searches you may run), such advertising may be related to the search terms you entered. We may present search result links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed and we may monitor click-throughs. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of our search technology. For instance, this data helps us determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results.

## 8 Your right to see your personal information

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold on you and to have any errors in that information corrected. We may charge a reasonable fee for such requests as permitted by law. Please address your request to Data Protection/Marketing, 150-152 King Street, Hammersmith, London, W6 0QU or email [contact@schoolsnet.com](mailto:contact@schoolsnet.com). We will use reasonable efforts to supply, correct or delete personal information about you on our files.
